Guide to the Consolidation Coal Company Records, 1854-1971 AIS.2011.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Predecessor & Subsidiary Companies' Minute Books, III.
  - Youghiogheny Coal Company, 195.
    - Minutes of Stockholders and Board of Directors Meetings, October 19, 1910-February 22, 1937 (Box 34)
- Stockholders' Records, IV.
  - Consolidation Coal Company, 1.
    - Notice of Annual Meeting and Proxy Statement, Annual Meeting of Shareholders, April 17, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Stock Certificate #1 (Issued to Mount Savage Iron Company for 6000 shares of capital stock at $100 per share.), May 13, 1864
    - Original Stock Certificate "A" (For 12,500 shares of capital stock issued to Allan Campbell and James Roosevelt, Trustees under a mortgage to them by Consolidation Coal Company.), January 21, 1879
    - Stock Certificates (Issued to Merchants Fire Assurance Corporation of N.Y, The North River Insurance Company, United States Fire Insurance Company, Samuel Mc Roberts, Trustee for Jere H. Wheelwright, Jr., and Clarence Wheelwright, William M. Wilshire, Chatham-Phenix National Bank and Trust Company, Dominick & Dominick, Edward C. DeVarennes, W. Herdman Schwatka, Isabel B. Robinson and Raymond B. Fosdick), September 2, 1924–November 4, 1943
    - Stock Certificates (Issued to John D. Rockefeller, Jr.), September 4, 1924
    - Common Stock- Public offering of 300,000 shares by the M.A. Hanna Company, March 1964 (Box 35)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company, 2.
    - Stock Certificates, July 17, 1916–June 19, 1958 (Box 35)
    - Stock Ledger, January 1, 1923-April 3, 1928
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company (New Jersey), 3.
    - 1916 Plan and Agreement of Readjustment (Box 35)
  - Associated Companies' Stock Records, Bound Volumes, 5.
    - Cassville & Monongahela Railroad Company Certificates, June 24, 1904-October 29, 1928 (Box 35)
    - Fairmont Coal Company Certificates (Volume 49), January 9, 1907-May 28, 1909 (Oversize 108)
    - Jamison Coal Company Certificates (Volume 50), July 1, 1892-April 15, 1900
    - Midland Coal Company Certificates (Volume 51), September 21, 1900-December 11, 1907
    - Monga Land Company Certificates, May 15, 1900-June 10, 1946 (Box 35)
    - The New Field Coke Company Certificates, January 23, 1907-July 15, 1912
    - The New Field Coke Company Certificates, July 15, 1912-December 12, 1929 (Box 36)
    - The Pennmont Coal Company Certificates, December 7, 1904-March 17, 1911
    - Pittsburgh & Castle Shannon Railroad Company Certificates (Volume 52), June 26, 1878-November 20, 1880 (Oversize 108)
    - Pittsburgh & Castle Shannon Railroad Company Payment Book, 1872-1880 (Box 36)
    - Pittsburgh & Fairmont Fuel Company Certificates, May 12, 1903-June 10, 1909
    - Pittsburgh Coal & Coke Company Certificates, May 31, 1906-May 19, 1914
    - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company Certificates (Volume 53), December 18, 1915-August 30, 1940 (Oversize 108)
    - Saw Mill Run Coal & Supply Company, December 20, 1902-October 15, 1913 (Box 36)
    - Soo River Coal Isle Company Certificates, January 4, 1909-March 23, 1935
    - Youghiogheny Coal & Coke Company Stock Ledger, Record & Transfer Book, September 12, 1903-July 20, 1907
- Financial Records, V.
  - Consolidation Coal Company General Ledgers, 1.
    - No. 1 (Volume 54), May 1, 1864-February 28, 1870 (Oversize 109)
    - No. 2 (Volume 55), March 1, 1870-December 31, 1876 (Oversize 110)
    - No. 3 (Volume 56), January 1, 1877-December 31, 1888 (Oversize 111)
    - No. 4 (Volume 57), January 1, 1889-December 31, 1896 (Oversize 112)
    - No. 5 (Volume 58), January 1, 1897–December 31, 1902 (Oversize 113)
    - No. 6 (Volume 59), January 1, 1903-December 31, 1905
    - No. 7 (Volume 60), January 1, 1906–December 31, 1908 (Oversize 114)
    - No. 8 (Volume 61), January 1, 1909-December 31, 1909
    - No. 9 (Volume 62), January 1, 1910-December 31, 1911 (Oversize 115)
    - No. 10 (Volume 63), January 1, 1912-December 31, 1913
    - No. 11 (Volume 64), January 1, 1914 – December 31, 1914 (Oversize 116)
    - No. 12 (Volume 65), January 1, 1917-December 31, 1919
    - No. 13 (Volume 66), January 1, 1920–December 31, 1921 (Oversize 117)
    - No. 16 (Volume 67), January 1, 1929–December 31, 1931
    - No. 17 (Volume 68), January 1, 1932 – June 2, 1932 (Oversize 118)
  - Consolidation Coal Company Journals, 2.
    - May 1, 1864 - December 31, 1868, microfilm?
    - No. 1 (Volume 69), January 1, 1869-September 30, 1874 (Oversize 119)
    - No. 2 (Volume 70), October 1, 1874-December 31, 1881 (Oversize 120)
  - Notice of Appeal, 3.
    - Consolidation Coal Company vs. Division of Water Resources, State Department of Natural Resources, West Virginia, April 5, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Newspaper & Magazine Articles, 4.
    - Coal Merger Now Approved by Objectors, Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, October 15, 1945 (Box 36)
    - 100 Million Assets of Coal Firm, Pittsburgh Sun-Telegraph, November 7, 1945
    - New Consolidation Coal Firm to Battle Competitive Fuels, no date
    - Paper Money US Air, April 1960
  - Payroll Records and Employee Benefits, 5.
    - Consolidation Coal Company: Long Term Disability Plan, no date (Box 36)
    - Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Company: Office Payroll Records, April 8, 1901-September 30, 1903
    - Pittsburgh Coal Company: Employee's Relief Department & Pension Fund, Advisory Committee Minutes (2 vols.), January 4, 1909-May 16, 1949 (Box 37)
    - Pittsburgh Coal Company: Employee's Relief Department & Pension Fund, Regulations & Amendments, October 24, 1946
    - Pittsburgh Coal Company: Service Annuity Fund Booklet, 1942
    - Pittsburgh Coal Company: Employee's Contributory Retirement Annuity Plan, July 1, 1944
    - Pittsburgh Consolidation Coal Company: General Office Payroll and Employees' Earnings Ledger Sheets, 1949-1950
    - United Mine Workers of America Welfare & Retirement Fund: Report for the Year Ending, June 30, 1971
- Secretary's Contract Files, VI.
  These files from the Office of the Secretary of the Pittsburgh Coal Company include mortgages, deeds, leases, and other contractual agreements. The original filing scheme has been preserved, with the files arranged in numerical order.
  - Wm Carpenter (Atlantic Trust Co of NY) and Pittsburgh Coal Company, November 1, 1899; 4. (Box 37)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company, December 5, 1899; 5.
  - Harriet McMillen and Nancy and Silas Tomlinson, March 5, 1895; 6.
  - Youghiogheny River Coal Co. and (Samuel Gilbert, Dillon Gibbons, Eliza Cope, Jesse Edgerton, and Sarah Gilbert), March 29, 1899; 7.
  - Imperial Coal Company and Mary E. Johnston et al., October 21, 1895; 8.
  - Ashtabula Coal Company - n.d., September 23, 1895-September 9, 1909; 9. (Oversize 127)
  - Railroad Cars- Sales and Leases, Feb. 20 & 25, 1897-July 27, 1909; 10. (Box 37)
  - Youghiogheny River Coal Company and Baltimore & Ohio RR Co., February 7, 1891; 11.
  - Montour Railroad Company and Southwest Pennsylvania Pipe Lines, August 29, 1891, July 25 and September 12, 1910; 12.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Dock Co. and Pittsburgh & Lake Erie RR Co., September 24, 1886-August 16, 1890; 13.
  - PCC and M.A.Hanna & Co. and Picklands Mather & Co, September 26, 1899, March 12, 1900, September 23, 1904, June 16, 1909; 14.
  - Wm. Beadling and Pittsburgh Coal Company, September 29, 1899; 15.
  - Milwaukee Dry Dock Co. and Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co, March 27, 1893, September 20, 1893, July-December 1895, July June 1, 1901; 16.
  - The Pittsburgh, Painesville & Fairport RR Co., the Pittsburgh, Fairport and Northwestern Dock Co. and the Pittsburgh & Western Railway Company, the Cleveland Terminal & Valley RR Company and the Pittsburgh Coal Company, January 30, 1897-August 19, 1903; 17.
  - Pittsburgh, Fairport and Northwestern Dock Co, October 1, 1887-May 25, 1909; 18.
  - Francis Robbins (Pittsburgh, Fairport & Northwestern Dock Co.) and John Pitcairn (same) and Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Company, January 5, 1895; 19.
  - Youghiogheny Gas Coal Co., December 1, 1899-December 1, 1903; 20. (Oversize 128)
  - U.A. Andrews and John Shaw, C. W. Baine and J. B. L Hornberger, November 17, 1899-August 18, 1900; 22. (Box 37)
  - Columbia Bridge Co.- November 26 1902, J.S. Bedell- August 24 1900, Finleyville Planning Mill Co.- November 21, 1902 with Pennsylvania Mining Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8 ), 24.
  - WH Roberts and Pennsylvania Mining Co., August 15, 1900; 25.
  - Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co. and John N. Mowry, August 19, 1900; 27.
  - Clifford Capell Fan Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, July 7, 1907; 28.
  - G. Dauenhauer & Sons Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 9, 1907; 30.
  - Sull Brothers and Pennsylvania Mining Co, October 3, 1900; 31.
  - Northwestern Coal Railway Co.- And Farmers Loan and Trust Company - May 1, 1893; And Pittsburgh Coal Company - October 17, 1899; Northwestern Coal Railway Co. - July 6, 1923., 31.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company, October 31, 1900-November 2, 1900; 33.
  - Bailey, Wilson & Co. and First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Company, May 31, 1894-September 21, 1895; 34.
  - Thomas Prosser and Pennsylvania Mining Co, September 18, 1900; 35.
  - PCC and Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad, April 9, 1942; 36.
  - Montour Shops, October 26, 1900-November 16, 1901; 39. (Box 38)
  - Robert E. Marshall and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, July 25, 1907; 41.
  - Charles P. Hickman, Violet J. Hickman, the Mercantile Trust Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, August 1, 1907; 42.
  - S.A. Cratsa and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 12, 1907; 43.
  - H. J. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, May 28, 1907; 44.
  - Youghiogheny Coal Co, June 11, 1892 - July 22, 1907; 46.
  - Youghiogheny & Elizabeth RR, May 9, 1884-May 22, 1900; 47-A.
  - Youghiogheny & Elizabeth RR, February 9, 1883-January 16, 1914; 47-B. (Oversize 122)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company & F.R. Buell Coal Co, October 10, 1900; 48. (Box 38)
  - First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co. and S.M. Willock and J.P. Willock. Mortgages and Bonds, December 1, 1894; 49.
  - Rodgers & Abel and Pennsylvania Mining Co (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), December 10, 1900; 50.
  - H.K. Wick, Yougiogheny Mining Co., Wick Haven Supply Co, H.K. Wick & Co. and Pennsylvania Mining Co., and Pittsburgh Coal Company, December 19, 1900; 54.
  - North Fayette RR Co, May 11, 1896; 55. (Oversize 127)
  - First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co. and Melissa M. Stelley (Certificate pulled to OS-126), December 17, 1894; 57. (Box 38)
  - Charles S. Barker, April 10, 1901; 59.
  - Snowden Coal Company, March 30, 1899; 61. (Oversize 128)
  - Vulcan Coal Co, December 23, 1896-June 8, 1897; 62. (Oversize 127)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., February 16-June 15, 1909; 63. (Box 38)
  - Vulcan Coal Co, June 8, 1897-October 21, 1903; 64.
  - First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co. and Rachel S. Rhodes, December 17, 1894; 65.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and W.J. Steen, September 28, 1907-September 25, 1915; 68 A-C.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and W.J. Steen (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), June 15, 1908-June 30, 1914; 68 D-F.
  - Valley Coal Transfer Co., April 1, 1897-May 29, 1902; 70. (Oversize 122)
  - Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co., April 3, 1894-April 7, 1914; 71. (Oversize 123)
  - Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co. and Fidelity Title & Trust Co., January 1, 1895; 72 A. (Oversize 122)
  - Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co., October 23, 1882-January 12, 1883; 72 B-N.
  - Pittsburgh & Chicago Gas Coal Co., January 29, 1893-July 15, 1897; 72 O-V. (Oversize 124)
  - Ellen H. Wilson and Pittsburgh Coal Company, September 25, 1907; 73. (Box 38)
  - Imperial Coal Co. and Union Trust Co. of Philadelphia, October 19, 1885-April 21, 1897; 74 A-B.
  - Imperial Coal Company, October 1, 1879; 74 E.
  - Port Royal Dock Co., October 20, 1897-May 2, 1919; 76. (Oversize 124)
  - Montour Telephone Co., December 17, 1903-December 21, 1903; 77.
  - Chartiers & Venetia Railroad Co., November 15, 1899-July 13, 1942; 78.
  - Greer & Van Emans R.R. Co., November 15, 1899-October 25, 1901; 79. (Oversize 125)
  - Canonsburg & Bishop Railroad Co., November 16, 1899; 80.
  - Montour & Gregg Railroad Co., November 15, 1899-1900; 82.
  - Houstonville Coal Railroad Co., November 27-28, 1899; 83.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Car Company, March 23, 1904-September 2, 1914; 84. (Box 38)
  - Black Diamond Railroad Co., November 29, 1899; 85. (Oversize 125)
  - Franklin Township Water Co., April 22, 1903; 86. (Box 38)
  - Federal Clay Products Co., June 7, 1905-May 3, 1922; 87.
  - Chartiers Valley & Northern Railway Co.(Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), April 28, 1902-July 13, 1942; 88. (Oversize 125)
  - Fort Pitt & Leasdale RR Co., April 2-3, 1900; 89.
  - Somers Coal Despatch Co., March 21, 1899-May 1, 1899; 90.
  - First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co.(Certificate pulled to OS-126), April 26, 1889-October 11, 1911; 91. (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Dock Co., November 5, 1886; 92. (Oversize 126)
  - Pittsburgh, Fairport & Northwestern Dock Co., March 15, 1899-January 4, 1935; 93.
  - F.M. Wallace, January 8, 1907; 94. (Box 39)
  - Manown Manufacturing Company (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), December 4, 1895-January 14, 1943; 95.
  - Bridgeville & Millers Run RR Co., November 15, 1899; 97.
  - Cedar Creek RR Co., August 5, 1905; 99.
  - Youghiogheny & Lehigh Coal Co., November 24, 1905-December 16, 1909; 100.
  - Monongahela River Coal & Coke Co., May 30, 1901-August 3, 1905; 102.
  - Cleveland Fuel Co., March 16-20, 1896; 105. (Oversize 126)
  - N.Y. & Cleveland Gas Coal Co.and Elkins Gas Coal Co., February 27, 1893-June 25, 1892; 106.
  - Albert McNillan and Pennsylvania Mining Co., October 12, 1901; 115. (Box 39)
  - Eliza J. Boyce and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 4, 1903-October 28, 1910; 118.
  - Shaner Coal Co., July 1, 1887-February 20, 1895; 122 A-I. (Oversize 126)
  - Shaner Coal Co., October 1, 1890-November 16, 1907; 122 J-N.
  - Shaw Coal Co. and Pennsylvania Mining Co., January 3, 1902-October 30, 1924; 124. (Oversize 127)
  - Elkins Gas Coal Co., March 7, 1892-March 17, 1913; 127.
  - Monon River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co., July 26, 1907; 128. (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh & Lake Erie RR. Co., December 31, 1907; 129.
  - Township of Chartiers, February 5, 1902; 130.
  - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 13, 1902; 132.
  - Copies of Charters-Various Corporations, April 3, 1870-August 15, 1898; 142.
  - Employee Liability Assurance Corporation Ltd. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 18, 1905 - January 18, 1906; 144.
  - Pennsylvania Mining Co. and Fort Pitt Gas Co., September 25, 1902-July 1, 1909; 146.
  - Pennsylvania Mining Co. and Owen Golden, November 7, 1902-January 6, 1920; 153.
  - Colonial Coke Co., February 9, 1900-April 7, 1914; 155. (Oversize 127)
  - Youngstown Ice Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 7, 1901-March 8, 1904; 156. (Box 39)
  - Philip Howell, Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Youghiogheny River Coal Co., May 4, 1904; 158.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Gayley Local Telephone Co., March 28, 1904-October 20, 1920; 159.
  - Mansfield Coal & Coke Co., November 22, 1864-February 11, 1913; 160. (Oversize 127)
  - George H. Rupp and Pittsburgh & Castle Shannon RR Co., May 2, 1904; 165. (Box 39)
  - Maynard D. Flinn and Pittsburgh Coal Company, October 4, 1907; 168.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Molamphy, October 14-November 2, 1907; 169.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Dock Co., June 2-3, 1904; 173.
  - Twin City Coal Yard Co., June 6, 1904; 174.
  - T. J. Donahoe and Youghiogheny Coal Co., Ltd., June 11, 1904; 175.
  - American District Telegraph Co. of Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh Coal Company, June 12, 1907; 176.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Detroit & Buffalo Steamship Co., March 30, 1904-April 1, 1909; 177.
  - Walsh-Upstill Coal Co., July 29, 1895-October 21, 1903; 182.
  - Mansfield Coal & Coke Co. and The Colonial Trust Co., October 15, 1903; 183.
  - J.J. Campbell and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, August 8, 1904; 187.
  - Pennsylvania R.R. Co. and Colonial Coke Co., May 10, 1904; 188.
  - Baltimore Storage & Distributing Co., March 6, 1900-February 7, 1908; 193. (Box 40)
  - Mifflin Coal Co. & New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 15, 1904-November 6, 1905; 198.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and The Franklin Township Water Co., July 27, 1904; 199.
  - Midland Coal Co., June 1, 1901-August 26, 1947; 200 A-F.
  - Midland Coal Co., May 15, 1912-August 23, 1912; 200 G-I.
  - Wm. E. Hamilton, W.R. Woodford, Francis L. Robbins et. al, January 1, 1903-May 15, 1907; 201.
  - H.F. Stark et. al. and Colonial Coke Co., February 26, 1903-February 21, 1905; 204 A-I.
  - H.F. Stark et. al. and Colonial Coke Co., April 21, 1903-December 9, 1903; 204 J-N.
  - James Patterson and Pennsylvania Mining Co., February 19, 1903; 205.
  - Borough of Houston, Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Midland Coal Co., November 17, 1905; 210.
  - W. E. Nusser and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 15-June 10, 1903; 213.
  - Alfred Tompkins and Pennsylvania Mining Co., June 9, 1903; 216.
  - F.J. Le Moyne and Henry R. Yates, February 1, 1927; 218.
  - David Hill and Greensboro Gas Co., January 29, 1910-April 30, 1941; 220.
  - William Walter et. al and First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co., October 25, 1893-April 5, 1905; 221.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Courtney Fire Brick Co., July 22, 1903; 223.
  - Imperial Brick Co, Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Montour Railroad Co., August 8, 1903; 225.
  - Owen Murphy and Franklin Township Water Co., September 19, 1903-August 3, 1904; 230.
  - Philip Gutbub and Pennsylvania Mining Co., October 1, 1903; 233.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co., Saw Mill Run Coal & Supply Co., December 11, 1904; 236.
  - Pennsylvania Mining Co. and M.B. Craighead, December 1, 1903; 238.
  - Joseph Walton's heirs and First Pool Monongahela Gas Coal Co., December. 11, 1897; 239.
  - Westmoreland Coal Co. and Pennsylvania Mining Co., December 24, 1903; 241.
  - Central District & Printing Tel. Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, November 17, 1899-February 8, 1917; 242 A.
  - Central District & Printing Tel. Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, November 11, 1899-January 12, 1929; 242 B.
  - Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, September 18, 1928-June 5, 1934; 242 B2.
  - Various Telephone Contracts and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 7, 1906- Aug. 12, 1918; 242 C. (Box 41)
  - Pittsburgh & Allegheny Telephone Co., June 29, 1910-March 5, 1923; 243 A.
  - Pittsburgh & Allegheny Telephone Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, January 29, 1901-December 13, 1921; 243 B.
  - Pittsburgh & Allegheny Telephone Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, May 23, 1903-April 25, 1939; 243 C.
  - Number changed to 1486, 244.
  - Louis Frank and Pennsylvania Mining Co., October 28, 1903; 245.
  - Federal Telephone Co. and Pennsylvania Mining Co., January 18, 1904; 246.
  - Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., Pittsburgh Coal Company and the Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co., March 1, 1905; 248.
  - Monongahela Saw & Planing Mill Company and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 23, 1905; 253.
  - National Dock & Fuel Co., October 23, 1901-January 17, 1905; 265.
  - Knoxville Land & Improvement Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, May 1, 1905; 267.
  - Federal Telephone Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 1, 1905; 279.
  - Canadian Northern Coal & Ore Dock Co., Mackenzie Mann & Co and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 1, 1905; 282.
  - Canadian & Northern Coal & Ore Dock Co., Canadian Northern Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Wisconsin, April 10, 1911; 282 A.
  - United States of America and Federal Clay Products Co., July 13, 1905; 285.
  - Federal Clay Products Co. and Isthmian Canal Commission and Munson Steamship Co., April 15, 1905 & September 14, 1905; 286.
  - Cozad, Beliz, Bates & Co., March 16, 1883-March 26, 1894; 289.
  - H.F. Stark and Colonial Coke Co., September 20, 1905; 291.
  - Rimouti Galliardi and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, October 12, 1905; 294.
  - F.G. Bishoff & Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Car Co., October 31, 1905; 297.
  - Wallis & Carley Co. and Colonial Coke Co., November 14, 1905; 300.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Henry Shenk Co., Jones & Laughlin Stick Co., Excelsior Terra Cotta Co. of New York, June 13, 1905-January 23,1906; 303.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Pan Handle Coal Co., Imperial Coal Co., February 7, 1905; 304.
  - Maryland, Pennsylvania & West Virginia Telephone Co. and the Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, January 29, 1907; 306.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Colonial Coke Co., December 18, 1905; 308.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, January 23, 1906; 313.
  - Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., January 18, 1906; 315.
  - Pittsburgh & Connellsville Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, December 27, 1905; 317.
  - Central District & Printing Telegraph Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, December 28-30, 1905; 319.
  - Carnegie Steel Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 28, 1905; 321.
  - John Stevenson & H.R. Harvey and the Pittsburgh Coal Company, December 5, 1900; 324.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 12 & 17, 1918, May 22, 1919; 327.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and McFarland Lumber Co., March 10, 1906; 328.
  - Mary E. Smock et. al. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, March 14, 1906; 329.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and Atlantic Refining Company, May 9, 1905; 334.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and John F. Hosack, March 28, 1906; 338.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company & Guiler Gas Coal Company, June 12, 1906; 339.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and A.M. Kinney, June 28, 1906; 343.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and Republic Iron and Steel Co., April 1, 1905-February 15, 1917; 344. (Box 42)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Monessen Coal & Coke Co., January 1, 1906; 345.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Witch Hazel Coal Company, July 6, 1906; 346.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Fayette Coal Company (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), July 20, 1906; 348.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and Monongahela Valley Electric Co, July 1, 1906; 349.
  - Pittsburgh-Buffalo Co., July 18, 1908-February 1910; 353.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company & Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., November 22, 1910-November 23, 1934; 356.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and Central Union Telephone Co., Akron Peoples Telephone Co., December 17-22, 1904; 361.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Walter A. Zelnicker Supply Co., September 26, 1906; 366.
  - Federal Clay Products Co. and Borough of West Elizabeth, PA, October 19, 1906; 367.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Hugh McHugh (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), November 8, 1906-January 20, 1927; 368.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Peter Wagner-, November 13, 1906; 370.
  - Central Coal & Dock Co., January 15-March 31, 1906; 371.
  - Western Union Telegraph Co and Pittsburgh Coal Company, October 1, 1906; 375.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Peter F. Hormel, October 1, 1906-December 28, 1910; 377 A-D.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Peter F. Hormel, December 28, 1910-January 19, 1911; 377 E.
  - The Bradstreet Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company, November 12, 1907-October 30, 1929; 379.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and John A. Linn, November 28, 1906; 380.
  - W.S. Lockhart et al. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania-December 27, 1906-March 28, 1935, 383.
  - Westmoreland Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania, January 4, 1907; 384.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company and The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, October 16, 1928; 386.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Company of Pennsylvania and Fred B & William S. Ollett, January 29, 1907-January 25, 1911; 388.